I knew something had to change because I had like a false sense of security because of my talent, because of success, because of religion.
I felt like I had made it.
You had the things.
Yeah, yeah.
You know, bi-coastal.
And I remember my cousin, I was like, I'm coming to New York.
And I showed up and I met him and he was like, where's your luggage?
I was like, I don't need luggage.
And he was like, yo, you don't even have to pack?
Like, you got it like that?
And I was like, oh, I guess I do.
I'm good.
I don't have to, like, I've made it.
Do you remember the age?
Oh, whenever I got divorced.
It was like right after I reached that.
And then I felt so lost because I was, how I looked at myself was directly related to being a husband, being what I thought a good father was.
And I was just like, I don't know where I am.
So you felt all these things when you were in the marriage, but then once you got divorced.
Yes.
And I had no idea that so much of who I was was attached to that.